RG 062:061, Town of Haddam
Connecticut State Library
Town of Haddam records
1904-1969
Connecticut State Library
Haddam (Conn.)
7 cubic feet
Tax records for the town of Haddam.
RG062_061
1985-028
Historical Note
The town of Haddam was incorporated on October 8, 1668.
Scope and Content
Tax records for the town of Haddam.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Haddam -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Haddam -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Haddam -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Haddam -- Registers
Places:
Haddam (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
Boxes 8 and 9 are restricted due to condition.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Tax Records, 1904-1969
  - Town of Haddam rate books, 1907-1915, 1917-1930, 1932-1934; 24 volumes (Box Box 1)
  - Town of Haddam rate books, 1935-1945; 12 volumes (Box Box 2)
    Contains an additional volume for 1942 marked "Special".
  - Town of Haddam rate books, 1946-1953; 8 volumes (Box Box 3)
  - Town of Haddam rate books, 1954-1959; 6 volumes (Box Box 4)
  - Town of Haddam rate books, 1960-1965; 6 volumes (Box Box 5)
    Volumes for 1964 and 1965 are marked "List of" on the covers.
  - Town of Haddam rate books, 1966-1969; 4 volumes (Box Box 6)
    Volumes for 1966 and 1969 are marked "List of" on the covers.
  - Higganum Fire District rate books, 1916-1948; 15 volumes (Box Box 7)
  - Suspense tax book of personal taxes, 1933-1945; 1 volume (Box Box 7)
  - Suspense tax books of property taxes, 1931-1950; 2 volumes (Box Box 7)
  - Unpaid real estate taxes for 1931, 1933; 1 folder (Box Box 7)
  - Town of Haddam rate books, 1904-1906; 3 volumes (Box Box 8)
    Restricted due to condition.
  - Town of Haddam rate book, 1916; 1 volume (Box Box 9)